pkjobvacancy.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy - Jobs Vacancy in Pakistan 2018

## [Privacy Policy](http://pkjobvacancy.com/privacy-policy/)

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which **Pkjobvacancy.com** collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (a ‘User’) of the **Pkjobvacancy.com**  website (‘Site’). Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information.

Pkjobvacancy.com respects the privacy and rights of its visitors and do not identify the visitor.

  * When a user visits Pkjobvacancy.com then the visitor’s Ip-address, Browser Version, location is stored on our servers. This information is stored for only statistical purpose and no other effort is made to identify the user.
  * Other information like visitors Phone number, Email address or name is not possible for Pkjobvacancy.com to log and this information is also not used for statistical purpose. Although this information is stored when user is an employer at Pkjobvacancy.com and tends to post jobs.
  * Those who share personal email at Pkjobvacancy.com, Their email address will not be sold or given to anyone.

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Cookies And Web Beacons

Our Site may use ‘cookies’ to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting[aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

Cookies and Web Beacons **Pkjobvacancy.com** does not use cookies.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

 **Pkjobvacancy.com** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **Pkjobvacancy.com** ’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.
